开萝尔:看孩子真麻烦.
Carol: This baby-care schedule really stinks.
本:你想吃麦片吗?
Ben: You gonna eat your cereal?
开萝尔:不.这不会麻烦你吧?
Carol: No. This doesn't bother you?
本:不会,如果我不用你勺子的话.
Ben: Not if I don't use your spoon.
迈克:早上好,不管是住在房子里的,还是住在洞穴里的.
Mike: Morning house dwellers! And cave dweller.
嘿,听着,妈妈上班之前有什么交待的吗?
Hey, listen, did Mom leave for work yet?
开萝尔:你关心什么?
Carol: What do you care?
迈克:你知道,这是她第一天离开孩子去上班,
Mike: Well, you know,
那肯定是一个精力充沛,
this being her first day back at work and away from the baby,
而又眼泪汪汪的场景……妈妈,
I predict this being one of those sappy, tear filled scenes,
爸爸!早上好!
that I for one... Mom! Dad! Good morning!
杰森:麦琪!你会首先觉得自己是如此无用,
Jason: Mike! I'm sure you're gonna feel rotten at first.
你会觉得你抛弃了你的孩子,是的,
You're gonna feel like you're abandoning your baby.
你会觉得,我是一个可怕的母亲!!!
Yes, you're gonna feel, I'm a terrible mother!!!
麦琪:哦,杰森.
Maggie: Oh Jason.
杰森:我很抱歉,我扯远了.对不起.
Jason: I'm sorry, I've gone too far. I'm sorry.
麦琪:我很好,只是给我一点时间.
Maggie: I'll be OK, just give me a minute.
杰森:嘿,我们正在给这些天排一个计划表,
Jason: Hey, we've been planning our schedule for days,
就像闹钟一样.看,我做了一块大木板,
it's gonna go like clock-work.
上面写了每一件事.好的,
Look at this; I got a big board made up and everything.
请注意!当我今天下午和病人在一起时,会怎么办?
Alright, attention please! What's gonna happen when I'm with patients
举手,开萝尔 西维尔!!
in the afternoon? Show of hands. Carol Seaver!!
开萝尔:我会在两点半放学,然后我直接回家,
Carol: I get out of school at two thirty;
照顾我唯一的妹妹.
I then come straight home and attend to my only sister's every need.
杰森:好的!!!当开萝尔不能直接到家时,迈克 西维尔!
Jason: Yes!!! And when Carol can't get right home, Mike Seaver!
迈克:我的狗吃了我的家庭作业,先生.
Mike: My dog ate my homework sir.
杰森:迈克.
Jason: Mike.
迈克:好的,我会用棍对付克莉丝.不,
Mike: Alright, I get stuck with Chrissy. I mean, I'll take care of Chrissy.
我是说,我来照看克莉丝.妈妈,
Mom, listen, you can count on me to do whatever it takes,
你让我做什么都可以,只要让小家伙健康,快乐.
to make sure that that little tyke is healthy, happy and gurgling spit.
杰森:在那些天里,当迈克因为某些学校或者法律的原因不能做到时,
Jason: And on those days when Mike can't make it,
本 西维尔.
for reasons that are hopefully school-related, or legal, Ben Seaver.
本:我来做,
Ben: I'll do it.
我只希望轮到我给克莉丝换尿布时,
I just hope that when it's my turn to change Chrissy's diapers,
不会有子弹光临这房间.
there's not a bullet in the chamber.
杰森:谢谢你的真心,本,
Jason: Thank you Ben, for that heart-felt sentiment.
麦琪,你看,我们都团结在一起.
Maggie, you see, we're all in this together.
事情一定会进展得很顺利,亲爱的.
Things are gonna work out great, sweetheart.
麦琪:哦,你是对的.
Maggie: Oh, you're right.
除此之外,你也会整天在这儿,
Besides, you'll be here the whole time too,
孩子白天大多数时候都会在睡觉.谢谢你,
and the baby should sleep most of the day anyway. Oh, thanks honey.
亲爱的,谢谢孩子们.
Thanks kids!!
迈克:再见,妈妈.
Mike: See you later Mom.
开萝尔和本:再见,妈妈!!!
Carol and Ben: Bye Mom!!!
迈克:再见,祝你好运!!
Mike: Goodbye, good luck!!
杰森:再见,妈妈.
Jason: Bye Mom.
麦琪:我会在她知道我走了之前回来(婴儿哭泣声),她知道了.
Maggie: I'll be back before she knows I'm gone. (Baby cries) She knows.
同事:哦,你好.填好这些表,中午交给我.但是在你做这些之前,斯利沃维奇先生很愿意见你.
Colleague: Oh hi. Here, fill these out, and get them back to me by noon
Oh, but before you do, Mr. Slivervich would like to see you
麦琪:我还担心没人想我呢.
Maggie: And I was worried nobody would miss me.
同事:我们都很想你,玛丽.
Colleague: Sure we missed you Mary.
麦琪:那是麦琪.我放弃了和我的孩子在一起.
Maggie: It's Maggie. I gave up spending time with my baby for this.
办公室人员:这太令人吃惊了!
Office workers: Surprise!!!!
麦琪:我爱你们,哦,我想念你们.
Maggie: I love you guys! Oh, I missed you!
(电话中)
(on the phone)
麦琪:我忘了这里的事情如何的紧张,压力,期限,办公室的勾心斗角……
Maggie: I'd forgotten how hectic things could be around here. The pressures, the deadlines, the office politics...
杰森:嘿,麦琪.
Jason: Hey Maggie, if I'd known things would got this smoothly with the baby,
如果我知道带孩子这么顺利,我应该早就把你踢出去了.
I would have kicked you out years ago.
麦琪:亲爱的,那可太好了.
Maggie: Honey, that's so sweet.
开萝尔:现在开萝尔正在回家的路上,我三点的病人还有半小时就要来,
Carol: Right now Carol's on her way home and my three o' clock hyperkinetic
所以,你要放松,高高兴兴回来.
won't be here for another half hour, so you just relax, enjoy being back.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的,我说过你很棒吗?
Maggie: Oh sweetheart, did I ever tell you that you're terrific?
警察:不用说得太多,不过……
Policeman: Not in so many words, but...
杰森:我爱你.
Jason: I love you.
麦琪:我不是在和你说.
Maggie: I wasn't talking to you.
杰森:那么你认为谁很棒吗?
Jason: Then who do you think is so terrific?
麦琪:杰森,别傻了,再见.
Maggie: You Jason, don't be silly. Bye.
杰森:我很高兴我打了.(放下电话)好了,伯姆巴兹先生,运动过度症,太紧张,走得太快……(婴儿哭泣声)爸爸来了,克莉丝,爸爸来了.(门铃响)当然,我的病人提前了,放松点,宝贝,放松点,伯姆巴兹先生,放松点!放松点!
Jason: I'm glad I called. (puts the phone down) Alright Mr. Bombazi, hyperkinetic, two tense
goes too fast, way too... (baby cries) Daddy's coming, Chrissy. Daddy's coming. (door bell rings
Of course, my hyperkinetic's early. Yoww, easy baby. Easy Bombazi, easy! Easy
(在和开萝尔的通话中)
(on the phone to Carol)
杰森:嘿,开萝尔,我要找到德比.
Jason: Hey Carol, look, I really need to find Debby.
不是德比,我要找到开萝尔,是的,
No, Debby, I need to find Carol, yeah. Err...
她应该半小时之前回来的……开萝尔 西维尔,我要找到她,
no she's supposed to be home a half an hour ago and...
我早就说过了.是的,我……迈克!
Carol Seaver, yes I'm trying to find her. I did say that in the first place.
迈克!嘿,迈克!
Yeah...I... Mike! Mike! Hey, Mike!
迈克:爸爸,爸爸,那不太……
Mike: Dad, Dad, it's not fair...
杰森:我需要你照看克莉丝.
Jason: I need you to take Chrissy.
迈克:爸爸,你看,爸爸,我了解小孩,但不是婴儿.
Mike: Dad, look, look, Dad, I know about babes, not babies.
杰森:我办公室有一个病人,看,
Jason: Yeah, well I've got...I've got a patient in my office, now look...
你看……她很喜欢你.
Look, there you see, she likes you.
迈克:如果她开始哭呢?
Mike: Women. What if she starts crying?
杰森:唱歌给她听.
Jason: Sing to her.
迈克:如果不管用呢?
Mike: And if that doesn't work?
杰森:给她喂奶.
Jason: Feed her.
迈克:如果仍然哭呢?
Mike: And what if she still keeps crying?
杰森:让她打嗝.
Jason: Burp her.
迈克:嘿!我不知道怎么让婴儿打嗝.
Mike: Hey! I don't know nothing about burping no baby.
杰森:迈克,我不会怪你.我现在没时间待在这儿和你争论.开萝尔不在这儿,你是下一位,我得和病人在一起.
Jason: Frankly Mike, I don't give a damn. Now come on, I haven't got time to stand here and argue with you. Carol's not here, you're next in succession, and I got to be with this patient.
迈克:好的.
Mike: Great.
本:嘿,迈克.
Ben: Hey Mike.
迈克:好的,嘿,本,你去哪儿了?
Mike: Yeah. Hey Ben, where the heck have you been?
本:哈?
Ben: Ha?
迈克:你知道爸爸不管了,开萝尔又逃避责任.
Mike: You know Dad is really ticked off! Carol ducked out of Chrissy duty.
本:责任?
Ben: Duty?
迈克:是的,你来填补.
Mike: Yeah. And you're supposed to be filling in.
现在我交给你了.
Now I've been covering for you.
本:开萝尔不在时是你,
Ben: You're supposed to take over when Carol's not here;
大木板上写着呢.
it's on the big board.
迈克:哦,本!除了爸爸,
Mike: Oh, come on Ben! You know no-one can read the big board but Dad.
没人看大木板.轮到你了,你去吧,
It's your turn. There you go, no need to thank me Benny, after all,
不必谢我,毕竟,
what are brothers for? Oh, and you might want to check if she needs to...
我们是兄弟.哦,你可以看一下她是否想要些什么……你知道的……
err...you know...
本:嘿,斯汀奇,你在这儿做什么?
Ben: Hey Stink, what are you doing here?
斯汀奇:我不知道,我那傻爸妈让我带这个礼物给克莉丝.我不明白我为什么一直拖到现在才拿过来.真的很奇怪……
Stink: I don't know. My stupid parents bought this stupid gift for Chrissy. I don't see why I should get stuck delivering it. It really weird...
本:慢着!等一下.你着急什么?过来,坐下,放松点.你想抱抱我的妹妹克莉丝吗?
Ben: Stay! Wait up. What's your hurry? Come on. Sit. Relax. Want to hold my sister Chrissy?
斯汀奇:好啊.
Stinky: Why not?
斯利沃维奇:麦琪,我要你去采访一个突发事件.
Slivervich: Maggie. I need you to cover a breaking story.
麦琪:现在?
Maggie: Now?
斯利沃维奇:是的,现在.这就是为什么称它为突发事件的原因.
Slivervich: Yes now. That's why it's called a breaking story.
麦琪:我很抱歉,斯利沃维奇先生,我不行,我还得回家照看孩子.
Maggie: I'm sorry Mr. Slivervich, I can't. I've got to get back to my baby.
斯利沃维奇:哦,她病了吗?
Slivervich: Oh, is he sick?
麦琪:没有.大木板上轮到我来解放杰森了.
Maggie: She. No, it's my turn on the big board to relieve Jason.
斯利沃维奇:大木板?
Slivervich: The big board?
麦琪:是的,斯利沃维奇先生,我很抱歉,但是我不行,我……
Maggie: Ah, yes, yes Mr. Slivervich. I'm sorry, but I can't. I uh...
斯利沃维奇:别多说了.我很希望有一个记者采访这次人质事件,
Slivervich: Say no more.
但是我理解.
I'd like to have had a reporter in this hostage situation, but I understand.
我是说,
I mean, when it's your turn on the old big board, it's your turn.
当大木板上轮到你时,你还怎么成为一位记者呢?
Walf, how would you like to be a reporter?
警察:那一直是我的梦想.
Policeman: Well it has always been my dream.
斯利沃维奇:好的.
Slivervich: Good.
警察:我可以带枪吗?
Policeman: Can I bring my gun?
麦琪:好的,我去.
Maggie: Ok, I'll do it.
警察:那好,我不带枪.
Policeman: Ok, I won't bring my gun.
杰森:看,对不起.你继续吧.
Jason: Yes, look, excuse me for a minute. You just go ahead.
病人:好,慢点,慢点,你得慢点.他用这种方式讨厌我.我说到哪了?
Patient: It's Ok, slow down, slow down. You got to slow down. He hates me by the way. Did I mention that?
斯汀奇:你好,西维尔医生,
Stinky: Oh, hi Doctor Seaver, this is a gift from my mum and dad.
这是我爸妈的礼物.他们说它可以帮助父亲们分担护理的过程.
They said it helps fathers can share the nursing process.
杰森:嗯.
Jason: Uh hu.
斯汀奇:很好的.
Stinky: It's kind of nice.
杰森:迈--克.
Jason: Mi-i-i-ike.
杰森:必须要谴责.你今天怎么样?
Jason: So damn clear. And how was your day?
麦琪:你还在和我说吗?杰森?
Maggie: Are you still talking to me? Jason?
麦琪:我在想.
Maggie: I'm thinking.
麦琪:震得很糟糕?
Maggie: Was it that bad?
杰森:我不得不取消今天的所有预约.
Jason: Well I had to cancel all my appointments for the rest of the day.
我发现斯汀奇 苏利文在给我们的孩子喂奶.
I got six loaded chambers.
相信我,
And to stop it all off, I found Stinky Sullivan breast feeding our baby.
你不会想知道的.
Trust me, you don't want to know about it.
麦琪:这些孩子在哪呢?我以为孩子们会帮忙呢.
Maggie: Well where are the kids? I thought the kids were going to help.
杰森:是的,我也这么想.看看这,
Jason: Yeah, so did I. Look at this, every name in its own colour.
每一人的名字都有自己的颜色,每一小时都有相应的颜色,没有冲突.
Every hour a corresponding colour. No clashes.
麦琪:板很漂亮.
Maggie: It's a beautiful board.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
麦琪:孩子们在哪呢?
Maggie: Where are the kids?
杰森:我认为他们在楼上迈克那.等你回来,
Jason: I think they are upstairs at Mike's place.
他们都躲起来了.他们想让你作为目击证人,
Waiting for you to come home. They are hiding.
这样我也许不会杀了他们.
They thought with you as a witness, maybe I won't kill them.
他们并不知道,我不怕坐牢.
Little do they know, the thought of prison doesn't bother me.
开萝尔:妈妈,我知道我应该打个电话说我要晚回来,但是我以为迈克在家……
Carol: Mum, I know I should have phoned to say I was going to be late, but I knew Mike was home and...
孩子们(同时说话)
Kids (talking at the same time.)
迈克:你怎么不让我们闭嘴?
Mike: Aren't you going to tell us to shut up?
你至少也要责备谁?来吧,
Aren't you at least going to blame somebody? Oh come on.
你发火吧?
Aren't you going to yell?
本:我去我的房间了.这太吓人了.
Ben: I'm going to my room. This is too spooky.
迈克:好的.我们安排好了,
Mike: Alright, alright. We get the picture.
他们关禁闭,我这个月不看有线电视.
They're grounded and I get no cable this month.
好吧,
Fine, no cable for two months.
两个月.在涨到三个月之前,
And I'm going to leave right this minute before it's three.
我得赶紧走了.一对气疯了的人!
How about a couple of hot heads!
麦琪:杰森,我们怎么做?
Maggie: Jason, what do we do?
杰森:好的,我想我们应该好好谈一谈,
Jason: Well I think its time we talked about a concept that we've never
我们从来没有真正的机会.
really given a fair chance.
麦琪:哦,杰森,我们不能丢下他们去牙买加.
Maggie: Oh Jason, we can't leave the kids and run off to Jamaica.
杰森:我没说这个.
Jason: I never thought of that.
麦琪:我是开玩笑.
Maggie: I was kidding.
杰森:好的,
Jason: Well I think that we should be hiring someone to come in here in
我认为我们应当雇一个人下午来这儿帮忙.
afternoons, and help out.
我知道我们总是说我们不想让一个陌生人来照看克莉丝,
I know we always said that we didn't want a stranger to raise Chrissy,
但是我不认为每天下午照看孩子两个小时有什么不妥.
but I don't think that a couple of hours of light house work and baby
你觉得呢?
sitting in the afternoon is exactly raising. What do you think?
麦琪:很好.
Maggie: Well.
杰森:什么很好?
Jason: Well what?
麦琪:杰森,也许我应该待在家里.
Maggie: Jason, maybe I should just stay home.
杰森:宝贝,别冲动,
Jason: Honey, come on. That's fatigue and emotions talking.
你知道你的工作很重要.
You know how important your career is.
麦琪:我只是想让你知道.哦,
Maggie: I just wanted to make sure you knew it too.
宝贝,
Oh honey, where do we get someone to do this?
我们去哪找人来呢?我是说这听起来可不好干.
I mean it sounds like a tough job to fill.
杰森:是的,尤其是最低工资.
Jason: Yeah, especially with minimum wage.
麦琪:谁说是最低工资?
Maggie: Who said anything about minimum wage?
杰森:我.宝贝,我们不是第一对面对这些的夫妻.我们找一些朋友,看报纸,找一些中介机构,我们得安排面试,会见这些人.
Jason: Me. Come on honey, we're not the first couple to face this. I'll call some friends, we'll look in the newspaper, we find some agencies, we'll set up interviews. We'll meet these people.
麦琪:好.星期五怎么样?
Maggie: Ok. How about Friday?
杰森:不,我星期五有预约.星期四吧?
Jason: No, I'm booked solid Friday. How about Thursday?
麦琪:不行,星期三.
Maggie: Can't. Wednesday.
杰森:不,星期三不行,星期二怎么样?
Jason: No. No way Wednesday. How about Tuesday?
麦琪:今天就是星期二.
Maggie: This is Tuesday.
杰森:那就再说吧.
Jason: So that's out.
麦琪:杰森,到我们都有空面试这些人的时候,
Maggie: Jason, by the time both of us get the chance to interview these
克莉丝都已经上大学了.宝贝,为什么你不自己来处理呢?
people, Chrissy will be in college. Honey, why don't you just handle it?
杰森:应该两个人.
Jason: We both should.
麦琪:我相信你的判断,毕竟,你选了一个好妻子.
Maggie: Now, I trust your judgment. After all, you did choose a great wife.
杰森:也许我只是运气.
Jason: Maybe I just got lucky.
麦琪:哦,真受不了.杰森,玉米和鸡肉.
Maggie: Oh, it's not worth it. Oh, Jason. Oh, Cornish game and hen.
朱莉:哒嘀嘀哒嘀(唱歌)
Julie: Dum dee dee dee dum dee (singing)
麦琪:你好.
Maggie: Oh Hello.
朱莉:你好,你肯定是西维尔太太.麦琪 马隆,新闻19频道的.
Julie: Hello. Oh, that must be Mrs. Seaver. Maggie Malone from news nineteen. Wow.
麦琪:谢谢你.你是?
Maggie: Thank you. Who are you?
朱莉:哦,我是朱莉 克斯特罗.
Julie: Oh yeah. I'm Julie Costello.
西维尔医生雇了我,照看孩子,还有其他一些事情.
Dr Seaver hired me to help out with the baby and everything.
麦琪:哦,他没有在电话里和我说起.
Maggie: Oh he didn't mention anything to me on the phone.
朱莉:他真是心细.他想给你一份惊喜.
Julie: Oh, he's so sweet. He wanted to surprise you with me.
麦琪:他做到了.我的丈夫今天面试了你,并且雇用了吗?
Maggie: Well he did. So my husband interviewed and hired you all today?
朱莉:是的.
Julie: That's right.
麦琪:这来得真快.
Maggie: Well, that happened very quickly.
朱莉:我知道.
Julie: I know.
麦琪:我很奇怪.
Maggie: I'm surprised.
朱莉:我也是.我的意思是电话里他说他今天不能做决定,
Julie: Me too. I mean on the phone he said that he couldn't make a decision
但是见了面之后,他问我能否今天就开始工作.
today, but after we met he asked if I could start this afternoon.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
朱莉:我最好得走了.现在克莉丝在房间睡觉呢.
Julie: I better run. Now Chrissy's asleep in her room.
麦琪:哦.
Maggie: Oh.
朱莉:晚餐过会就好了.
Julie: And dinner will be ready in just a few minutes.
麦琪:你做了饭.
Maggie: You cooked dinner.
朱莉:嗯.我明天两点过来,代我向杰森说再见吧.
Julie: Uh hu. I'll be back tomorrow at two. And tell Jason goodbye from me.
麦琪:杰森!
Maggie: Jason!
朱莉:哦,是他让我这么称呼的,
Julie: Oh, well that's what he wants me to call him.
我觉得非常不合适.麦琪.
I don't feel very comfortable doing it, Maggie.
麦琪:可以称呼麦琪.
Maggie: Mags will be fine.
朱莉:再见.
Julie: Bye.
麦琪:再见.
Maggie: Bye.
杰森:麦琪,你回来了.
Jason: Maggie, you're home. Darn.
麦琪:回来了!
Maggie: Darn!
杰森:好的,我有件惊喜给你.
Jason: Yeah well, I had a little surprise for you.
麦琪:我看到她了.
Maggie: I met her.
杰森:好的,太好了.她很不错吧?
Jason: Oh yeah. Great. Isn't she great? She's a bundle of energy.
她充满了活力,今天我每次从办公室出来,她都在做事.
Every time I came out of the office today, she was doing something different.
麦琪:她真的很棒,嘿,杰森?
Maggie: So she's a regular miracle worker, hey Jason?
杰森:她在本的屋里洗了衣服.
Jason: Well she did part the clothes on Ben's floor.
每天三小时的工作怎么样?
So how was day two at work?
麦琪:不要换话题,杰森 西维尔.
Maggie: Don't try to change the subject with me Jason Seaver.
杰森:什么?
Jason: Pardon me?
麦琪:现在我筋疲力尽地回来,发现你已经雇好了人,完全是你的决定.
Maggie: No I come home exhausted from work and find you've hired someone all on your own.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Right.
麦琪:这是怎么回事呢?
Maggie: What's going on here?
杰森:我不知道.我们吃饭时再谈吧.玉米和鸡肉.
Jason: I'm not sure. Well we can talk about it over dinner. Cornish game hen.
本:朱莉在哪?
Ben: Where's Julie?
杰森:她刚走.
Jason: She just left.
本:哦,天哪.
Ben: Oh nuts.
麦琪:怎么了?
Maggie: What's wrong?
本:我们要一起锻炼的.
Ben: We were going to exercise together.
杰森:本,你讨厌锻炼.
Jason: Ben you hate exercise.
本:不讨厌了.
Ben: Not anymore.
杰森:我认为那很不错.
Jason: Uh. I think that cute.
麦琪:朱莉也是.
Maggie: So is Julie.
杰森:是的.
Jason: Yeah.
麦琪:你好,开萝尔.
Maggie: Hi Carol.
开萝尔:再见,妈妈.
Carol: Bye mum.
麦琪:别弄得没胃口,还有丰盛的晚餐等着呢.
Maggie: Don't spoil your appetite with this gourmet dinner waiting.
开萝尔:哦,朱莉已经给我们做了饭.太好了.
Carol: Oh Julie already cooked dinner for us. It was great.
杰森:开萝尔,你知道,
Jason: Carol, you know,
在朱莉之前,也有人做过一次或者两次很棒的晚餐.
someone has cooked a good meal or two around here before Julie.
开萝尔:我很抱歉.我说错话了.
Carol: I'm sorry, that was very insensitive of me.
爸爸,你做饭也很不错.
Dad, you're a wonderful cook too.
杰森:吃完晚餐之后,你会感觉更好的.
Jason: You're going to feel a lot better after a good meal. Come on honey.
宝贝,不要这样,
Now don't get carried away.
这儿少不了你,和以前一样.
You are just as needed around here as you ever were.
迈克:哦,妈妈.
Mike: Oh hi mum. Listen, did you meet that outrageous fox that dad hired?
听着,你看见爸爸雇的那个狐狸精了吧?知道吗?
Know what, she even did my laundry for me.
她还给我洗衣服.最后这儿所有的东西都井井有条了.
Finally things are running right around here.
杰森:如果你不想吃玉米鸡肉的话,
Jason: Hi. Well if you don't want the Cornish Game Hen,
你至少应该吃些这个.工作不顺利吗?
you should at least have this. Bad day at work? Wo.
喔.
You know all this exercise is really paying off.
这种锻炼很有效,你会很快恢复苗条身材的.
You are going to have your old figure back in no time.
这话说得有点唐突.
Half way through that sentence I knew I was a dead man.
麦琪:听着,我知道我没有以前苗条了.
Maggie: Look, I know I don't have my pre-baby figure back.
杰森:哦,宝贝,我爱你,不管你有多胖……不,不.
Jason: Oh honey, I love you no matter how big ...no, no, no.
麦琪:杰森,你考虑过跑步吗?
Maggie: Jason, have you ever thought about jogging?
杰森:我跑步.
Jason: I do jog.
麦琪:我是说现在.
Maggie: I meant now.
杰森:麦琪,为什么,我觉得你不喜欢朱莉?
Jason: Maggie, why is it, for some reason, I get the sense that you don't like Julie?
麦琪:哦,你在意了?
Maggie: Oh, look out Creskin.
杰森:我只是不明白,我意思是说,
Jason: I just don't understand it.
她是哥伦比亚大学的学生,
I mean she's a soft more at Columbia University,
主修儿童心理学,
majoring in child psychology;
她一手带大了五个弟弟.让她来的那个中介机构,
she practically raised five brothers single handedly.
把她说得没法再好了,她一抱克莉丝,
The agent that sent her over couldn't say enough nice things about her
克莉丝就不哭了.
and the moment she picked Chrissy up, Chrissy stopped crying.
麦琪:那就打动了你.
Maggie: And that impressed you.
杰森:麦琪.
Jason: Maggie.
麦琪:杰森,你能告诉我你一点也没有注意到她的样貌吗?
Maggie: Jason, are you telling me that you didn't notice her looks at all?
杰森:当然,我看到了.
Jason: Of course I did.
麦琪:那你为什么不承认?你喜欢漂亮的女人.
Maggie: Hu! Why don't you admit it? You like beautiful women.
杰森:有罪吗?
Jason: Guilty.
麦琪:你.
Maggie: Men.
杰森:麦琪,我不是轻率地做出这个决定的,
Jason: Maggie, I did not take this decision lightly.
我今天面试了一吨的人.
I interviewed a ton of people today.
麦琪:一吨.有多少?
Maggie: A ton. How many?
杰森:四个
Jason: Four.
麦琪:哦,那么除了朱莉,其他三个都很胖了.
Maggie: Oh, so that makes Julie and, uh, three very large women.
杰森:麦琪,如果我只看样貌的话,
Jason: Maggie, if I were hiring strictly on looks,
我应该雇用第二个女人.哦!
I would have taken the second woman I saw. Oh!
麦琪:你今天很快活啊.
Maggie: Well you had quite a day.
杰森:我以为我们昨晚决定了我来做这个,麦琪.我幸运地碰到了朱莉,我为什么不要呢?
Jason: I thought we decided last night that I would handle this Maggie. I can't help it if I got lucky with Julie.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:你知道……我以为我找了这样的一个人,你会很开心.
Jason: You know what...I thought you'd be happy that I found someone who's so, so..
麦琪:年轻而又漂亮.
Maggie: Young and pretty.
杰森:很明显我错误地判断了你看到朱莉时的反应.
Jason: Well clearly I misjudged the way you'd react to Julie.
麦琪:算了,杰森.
Maggie: Bingo Jase.
杰森:哦.不应该只谈论她长得怎样.
Jason: Oh come on. This can't all be about the way she looks.
她工作的不也很好吗?
Is everything alright at work?
麦琪:是的,该是你问了.
Maggie: Well it's about time you asked.
杰森:我问过你了,麦琪.第一次……哦,你是对的.
Jason: Oh I did ask Maggie. The first time... oh. Ok, you're right.
麦琪:杰森,你知道吗,我已经三个月没上班了,接着以前拉下的活.我已经十五年没有这样了.你能体会吗?我两三分钟就会提到孩子,摄影师一边装他的三脚架,一边说"孩子真的太厉害了",于是我开始哭.等我回到家,我被告知不需要我做任何事,我帮不了什么忙.我还发现,厨房的桌子从冰箱那儿向外移动了十一点五英寸.
Maggie: Jason, do you have any idea what it's like going back to work, going back to work three months behind where I started from. Which was fifteen years behind to begin with. And did you realize that the word baby pops up every three point two minutes? The camera man was putting his camera on his tripod, and he said "this baby is sure heavy" and I started to cry. And then I come home and I'm told I don't need to do anything. I'm told things haven't ever run better. And then I find that the kitchen table is eleven and five inches further away from the refrigerator.
杰森:我很抱歉,很抱歉,我没想到你会觉得这么不安全.
Jason: I'm sorry, I'm sorry. I didn't know you'd be so insecure.
麦琪:我不是不安全.我已经四十岁了,
Maggie: I am not insecure. What I am is forty years old.
体重超出10磅了,而且很累.我不会不安全.
Ten pounds over weight, and incredibly tired. And I am not insecure.
杰森:亲爱的,来这儿.我可以尽我所能,只要你能感觉好一点.
Jason: Sweetheart, come here. I am going to do anything I possibly can to make you feel better.
麦琪:真的?
Maggie: Really?
杰森:当然.
Jason: Of course. I mean it.
麦琪:哦,杰森,太好了,
Maggie: Oh Jason, that's so sweet, that's so sweet. Thank you.
太好了.谢谢你,我会帮你找个人代替朱莉.
And I'll help you find Julies replacement.
杰森:你想让我解雇朱莉?宝贝,这样不公平.
Jason: You want me to fire Julie? Honey that is not fair.
麦琪:好的,我只是认为我们可以找到更好的.
Maggie: Well I just think that we can find somebody better.
有些人更有经验,有些人更能吃苦.
Someone with more experience. Someone weathered.
杰森:她已经够好了.
Jason: Mr. Belvedere already has his own show.
麦琪:我认为我们可以找到更好的,只要我们出的钱高出最低工资.
Maggie: And I think we can do a whole lot better if we pay above minimum wage.
杰森:嘿,朱莉的工资已经超出了最低标准一点点.
Jason: Hey, well, Julie gets a little more than minimum wage.
麦琪:一点点.
Maggie: A little more.
杰森:两倍.
Jason: Double.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What?
杰森:让人带孩子,我们不可能出得这么少.我想你如果多了解他一点,就会喜欢她.你这样对她不公平.
Jason: We can't be cheap skates when it comes to child care. I think you'll like her if you just get to know her a little bit. You haven't given her a fair shake.
麦琪:我希望你不会.
Maggie: And I sure hope you haven't.
杰森:是的,麦琪,如果你很坚决的话,让朱莉走.但是你得看着她的眼睛,告诉她她被解雇了.
Jason: Yeah right, Maggie, if you feel that strongly about this, Julie is gone. But you're going to be the one to look her right in the eye and tell her she's fired.
麦琪:很好!恶人我来做.
Maggie: Fine! Make me the heavy.
迈克:嘿,本,
Mike: Hey Ben, look.
看.如果你拉我来这只是为了看新闻里的妈妈,
If you dragged me down here to just to see mum on the news,
我得告诉你,我不感兴趣.
I got news. I'm not interested.
本:你会的,坐下来,朱莉,妈妈出现了!
Ben: You will be. Sit down. Julie, mums on!
朱莉:哦,我很高兴你喊我.
Julie: Oh I'm glad you called me.
电视:麦琪?
TV: Maggie?
朱莉:谁又把它扔在地上了?
Julie: What's this rattle doing down here again?
迈克:我也很高兴你喊我.
Mike: I'm glad you called me too.
朱莉:嘘!她来了.
Julie: Shh! She's o.
麦琪(电视中):业主说不会理会大楼的规定,他要使用这些锋利的铁丝网,
Maggie on TV: And the land lord said regardless of the building code,
除非,用他的话讲,"
he will be using these razor sharp coils until,
这些疯癫的鸽子得会到自己的家".这是新闻19频道的麦琪?马隆为你做报道.
and I quote "these screwy pigeons go home where they belong.
该你了,卢克.
This is Maggie Malone for news nineteen. Back to you Luke.
卢克(电视中):麦琪,提到回家,
Luke on TV: Maggie, speaking of going home,
业主们想过那些鸽子去哪吗?
did the landlord have any thoughts as to where these pigeons should go?
麦琪?麦琪?
Uh Maggie? Maggie?
麦琪:哦,很好,你还在这儿.
Maggie: Oh Good. You are still here.
朱莉:是的,快收拾完了.
Julie: Yeah, just finishing up.
麦琪:你能放下我丈夫的短裤吗?请你.我是说我们可以坐下来谈谈.
Maggie: Can you drop my husband's shorts please. I mean can we sit and talk.
朱莉:当然可以.你想谈什么?
Julie: Sure. What's on your mind?
麦琪:我想我得尽快说.
Maggie: I should just say this as quickly as I can.
朱莉:我不急.
Julie: Oh I'm in no hurry.
麦琪:我着急.朱莉,你是一名大二的学生,对吗?
Maggie: Well I am. Julie, you're a sophomore, right?
朱莉:是的.
Julie: Uh hu.
麦琪:我想说的是……
Maggie: Well what I want to say is...
朱莉:但是我两年以后可能不会毕业,
Julie: But I may not graduate in two years.
我正在考虑更改我的心理学专业.
I've been thinking about changing my psych major.
麦琪:哦,那会是……
Maggie: Uh hu. See well the thing is that I...
朱莉:新闻学.
Julie: Journalism.
麦琪:什么?
Maggie: What about it?
朱莉:我想换成新闻学.
Julie: Well that's what I'm thinking of switching to.
麦琪:很好.回到我的主题吧.
Maggie: Good. Well back to my point. See....
你在考虑把心理学换成新闻学?
You're thinking of switching from Psychology to Journalism?
朱莉:是的.
Julie: Uh hu.
麦琪:我做的就是那个.
Maggie: Well I did the same thing.
朱莉:真的?
Julie: Really?
麦琪:是的.但是我大一时候还没有,
Maggie: Yeah. But I didn't do it till the first semester of my junior year.
在我一接触到新闻学以后,我就被它迷住了.
See after I got a taste of journalism, I was hooked.
朱莉:出版还是电视新闻?
Julie: Print or TV news?
麦琪:不,我首先喜欢的是出版,但是我上了电视之后,我开始认为这才是真正我要的.
Maggie: No, my first love is print, but since I've been on the air I'm starting to think that this could really be my....
朱莉:归宿?
Julie: Babywick?
麦琪:哦,我跑题了.
Maggie: Oh, I'm off my point.
朱莉:对不起,我们可以以后再谈.
Julie: Sorry. We can talk about this later.
麦琪:嗯,朱莉,
Maggie: Uh hu. Julie, let me start this another way.
我们还是换一种说法.
See sometimes you can do all the right things on a job,
你有时候做的很不错,
and just because you happen to be who you are,
只是因为碰巧你是这样的人,你可能使得雇你的人……
you can make the people who hired you....
朱莉:不好意思.蛋奶酥好了?
Julie: Excuse me. That's the soufflé?
麦琪:好了.我们现在能忘记蛋奶酥吗?
Maggie: Perfect. Can we forget the soufflé for now?
朱莉:很抱歉,你说?
Julie: Sorry, you were saying?
麦琪:我不确信.
Maggie: I'm not sure.
朱莉:你说"你有时候做的很不错,只是因为碰巧你是这样的人" ……你觉得我有可能成为一个好的记者吗,或者其他什么的?有什么问题吗?
Julie: You said "sometimes you can do all the right things on a job, and
just because you are who you are, people can.....Ding! Do I have the makings
of a good reporter or what? There's something wrong, isn't there
麦琪:你也有精神病学家的潜质.
Maggie: You've got the makings of a psychologist too.
朱莉:杰森也这么说.
Julie: That's what Jason told me.
麦琪:我想起来了.
Maggie: Now I remember my point.
朱莉:关于你的丈夫?
Julie: So this is about your husband?
麦琪:我希望不.我是说不.
Maggie: I hope not. I mean no.
朱莉:他整个时间都在谈你.
Julie: He talks about you all the time.
麦琪:他?
Maggie: He does?
朱莉:麦琪这样抱克莉丝,会让她安静.
Julie: Maggie holds Chrissy this way to quiet her.
我和病人在一起时麦琪打电话了吗?麦琪从来不让迈克这样做.
Did Maggie call while I was with a patient?
我告诉你,
Maggie would never let Mike get away with that.
我想他在你上班之后,真得很想你.
I'll tell you, I think he really misses you now that you're back at work.
麦琪:你认为呢?
Maggie: Do you think?
朱莉:我觉得他有一点妒忌.
Julie: Between us, I think he's a little jealous.
麦琪:因为什么?
Maggie: Of what.
朱莉:我是说他必须和整个城市分享你,
Julie: I mean he has to share you with the whole city.
大多数的男人对于分享他们的妻子都会感觉不安全.
Most men would be too insecure to share their wives.
麦琪:大多数的女人也是如此.
Maggie: Most women too.
朱莉:什么?
Julie: Pardon me?
麦琪:不安全感会让你疯掉的,我听说过.
Maggie: Insecurities can drive you crazy. So I've heard.
朱莉:像那样的丈夫,你的家庭,
Julie: Boy, a husband like that, your family, dream job. You've got it all.
一个梦想的工作,你得到了全部,我觉得太不可思议了.
I didn't think it was possible.
麦琪:我也是.
Maggie: Neither did I.
朱莉:我很抱歉,我又换了话题.你想说什么?
Julie: I'm sorry. I changed the subject again. You were going to say?
麦琪:你被解雇了.
Maggie: You are fired.
朱莉:什么?
麦琪:开个玩笑.
00:23:35,100
Julie: What? Maggie: Just kidding.